练习 9-3：请跟读段落中的 Z 音。
Exercise 9-3. All's well that ends well. Repeat the Z sounds in the paragraph
below. A lazy Thursday at the zoo,
found the zebras grazing on zinnias,
posing for pictures,
and teasing the zookeeper, whose nose was bronze by the sun.
The biggest zebra's name was Zachary, but his friends called him Zach. Zach was a
confusing zebra whose zeal for reason caused his cousins, who were naturally
unreasoning,
to pause in their conversations.
While they browsed, he philosophized. As they grazed, he practiced Zen. Because
they were Zack's cousins, the zebras said nothing, but they wished he would muzzle
himself at times.